BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Millmen - Houston, TX, 1918-1920 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Millmen - Cincinnati, OH, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Millmen - Portland, OR, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Millmen - Ft. Worth, TX, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Mule Spinners - Providence, RI, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Ocean Marine Engineers - n/a, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Marine Engineers - Seattle, WA, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- Marine Engineers - Honolulu, HA, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 95)
- Marine Engineers - Evansville, IN, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 96)
- Marine Engineers - New York, NY, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Marine Engineers - Whitehall, NY, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Marine Engineers - Galveston, TX, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Marine Engineers - Norfolk, VA, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Marine Engineers - Savannah, GA, 1921-1923 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  1921, 1923
- Marine Engineers - Memphis, TN, 1920-1923 (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Marine Engineers - Charlotte, SC, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Marine Engineers - Toledo, OH, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Marine Engineers - San Francisco, CA, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Mattress and Upholstered Box Spring Bed Makers - New York, NY, 1923-1926 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Mattress and Box Spring Makers - Newark, NJ, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Machine Painter and Color Mixers - n/a (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Moving Picture Operators - Boston, MA, 1914-1924 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  1914, 1918, 1922, 1924
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Portland, OR, 1919-1923 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  1919, 1920, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Lansford, PA, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Little Rock, AR, 1916-1919 (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Detroit, MI, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Kansas City, MO, 1917-1928 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  1917-1919, 1922-1924, 1928
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - St. Louis, MO, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Butte, MT, 1917-1923 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  1917, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Omaha, NE, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Buffalo, NY, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Providence, RI, 1916-1920 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  1916, 1919, 1920
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Chattanooga, TN, 1920-1925 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  1920, 1925
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Memphis, TN, 1917-1925 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  1917, 1922-1925
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Milwaukee, WI, 1918-1919 (Box 4, Folder 122)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Scranton, PA, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Pittsburgh, PA, 1917-1923 (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Philadelphia, PA, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Fall River, MA, 1917-1923 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  1917, 1918, 1920, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Dayton, OH, 1919-1922 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  1919, 1922
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Cleveland, OH, 1912-1919 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  1912, 1919
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Albany, AL, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 129)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Baltimore, Mary., 1915-1925 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  1915, 1918, 1923, 1925
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - New Orleans, LA, 1917-1924 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  1917, 1922, 1924
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Lake Charles, LA, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 132)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Louisville, KY, 1916-1920 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  1916, 1917, 1919, 1920
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Dallas, TX, 1917-1923 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  1917, 1918, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Nashville, TN, 1923-1924 (Box 4, Folder 135)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Salt Lake City, UT, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 136)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Houston, TX, 1915-1917 (Box 4, Folder 137)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Wichita, KS, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 138)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Toledo, OH, 1922-1923 (Box 4, Folder 139)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - New York, NY, 1918-1923 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  1918, 1919-1920, 1922-1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Rochester, NY, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 141)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Utica, NY, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 142)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Springfield, MA, 1917-1919 (Box 4, Folder 143)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - San Francisco, CA, 1919-1923 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  1919, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Davenport, IA, 1917-1923 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  1917, 1922, 1923
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Denver, CO, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 146)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Los Angeles, CA, 1918-1927 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  1918-1920, 1922-1923, 1925, 1927
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Ft. Wayne, IN, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 148)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Minneapolis, MN, 1916-1919 (Box 4, Folder 149)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Lowell, MA, 1923-1924 (Box 4, Folder 150)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Grand Rapids, MI, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 151)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Jacksonville, FL, 1919-1927 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  1919, 1923, 1927
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Washington D.C., 1917-1924 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  1917, 1918, 1922-1924
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - New Haven, CT, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 154)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Bridgeport, CT, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 155)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Pueblo, CO, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 156)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Spokane, WA, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 157)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Seattle, WA, 1918-1922 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  1918, 1922
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Pittsfield, MA, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 159)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Kansas City, KS, 1920-1923 (Box 4, Folder 160)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators - Cincinnati, OH, 1918-1923 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  1918, 1919, 1920, 1923
- Cellar Packers - Union Pacific RR, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Newsboys - Everett, WA, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Writers - Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Packing House - Chicago, IL, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Painters - Reading, PA (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Painters - Baltimore, Mary., 1911 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Painters - n/a, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Paper Cutters - New York, NY, 1912-1925 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Paper Handlers - New York, NY, 1923-1925 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Paper Makers - Sturgeon Falls, Ontario, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Paper Rulers - Philadelphia, PA, 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Paper Rulers - New York, NY, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Paper Rulers - St. Louis, MO, 1916-1919 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Paper Rulers - Chicago, IL, 1912-1919 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Stone, Brick, Wood Block Pavers and Rammermen - Cleveland, OH, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Pavers, Rammersmen - New York, NY, 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  1926, 1927
- Paving Cutters - Chester, MA, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Paving Cutters - Albion, NY, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Paving Cutters - Boston, MA, 1922-1927 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  1922, 1923, 1927
- Paving Cutters - Milford, NH, 1905-1922 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  1905, 1922
- Paving Cutters - Concord, NH, 1923-1925 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Paving Cutters - St. Louis, MO, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Paving Cutters - Minneapolis, MN, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Paving Cutters - Rockport, MA, 1916-1925 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  1916, 1925
- Paving Cutters - Willard's Point, ME, 1916-1925 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Paving Cutters - Vinalhaven, ME, 1916-1928 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  1916, 1928
- Paving Cutters - Sullivan, ME, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Paving Cutters - Boston, MA, 1922-1923 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Paving Cutters - Santa Rosa, CA, 1906 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Paving Cutters - Oneco, CT, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Paving Cutters - Stonington, ME, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Paving Cutters - Waterford, CT, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Paving Cutters - Stone Mountain, GA, 1905-1927 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  1905, 1924, 1927
- Paving Cutters - Augusta, ME, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Paving Cutters - Hallowell, ME, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Paving Cutters - St. Cloud, ME, 1904-1925 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  1904, 1916, 1923, 1925
- Paving Cutters - Sandstone, ME, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Paving Cutters - Minturn, ME, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Paving Cutters - Holley, NY, 1904-1905 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  1904, 1905
- Paving Cutters - Orleans County, NY (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Paving Cutters - Granite Quarry, NC, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Paving Cutters - Mt. Airy, NC, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Paving Cutters - Torrance, PA, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Paving Cutters - Westerly, RI (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Paving Cutters - Barre, VT, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Paving Cutters - Sodom, VT, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Paving Cutters - Red Granite, WI, 1922-1924 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  1922, 1924
- Paving Cutters - Millstone, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Pharmacists - Stockton, CA, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  Missing
- Pharmacists - San Francisco, CA, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Piano, Organ and Musical Instruments - Chicago, IL, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Piano, Organ and Musical Instruments - Portland, OR, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Piano, Organ and Musical Instruments - Oakland, CO, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Photo Engravers - Philadelphia, PA, 1916-1924 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  1916, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1924
- Photo Engravers - Denver, CO, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Photo Engravers - San Francisco, CA, 1911-1921 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  1911, 1912, 1921
- Photo Engravers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1917-1924 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  1917, 1924
- Photo Engravers - Providence, RI, 1916-1927 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  1916, 1920, 1924, 1927
- Photo Engravers - Dallas, TX, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Photo Engravers - Houston, TX, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Photo Engravers - San Antonio, TX, 1919-1928 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  1919, 1928
- Photo Engravers - Salt Lake City, UT, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  1919, 1920
- Photo Engravers - Richmond, VA, 1917-1922 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  1917, 1920, 1922
- Photo Engravers - Seattle, WA, 1905-1926 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  1905, 1918, 1919, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Spokane, WA, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Photo Engravers - Milwaukee, WI, 1916-1920 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Photo Engravers - Washington, OR, 1919-1925 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  1919, 1920, 1925
- Photo Engravers - Kentucky, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Photo Engravers - Texas, 1916-1921 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  1916, 1919-1921
- Photo Engravers - Denver, CO, 1916-1921 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  1916-1917, 1919, 1921
- Photo Engravers - New Haven, CT, 1917-1921 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  1917, 1920, 1921
- Photo Engravers - Kansas City, KS, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Photo Engravers - Chicago, IL, 1900-1925 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  1900, 1903, 1906, 1915, 1918-1925
- Photo Engravers - Rockford, IL, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Photo Engravers - Ft. Wayne, IN, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Photo Engravers - San Francisco, CA, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Photo Engravers - n/a, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Photo Engravers - Los Angeles, CA, 1903-1925 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  1903, 1913, 1918, 1919, 1925
- Photo Engravers - San Diego, CA, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Photo Engravers - New York, NY, 1914-1927 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  1914, 1916, 1917, 1919, 1920-1927
- Photo Engravers - Milwaukee, WI, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Photo Engravers - Albany, NY, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Photo Engravers - Cleveland, OH, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Photo Engravers - Columbus, OH, 1915-1926 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  1915, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Dayton, OH, 1914-1926 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  1914, 1915, 1920, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Springfield, OH, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Photo Engravers - Chicago, IL, 1904-1925 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  1904, 1916, 1920, 1925
- Photo Engravers - Boston, MA, 1919-1924 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  1919, 192, 1922-1924
- Photo Engravers - Baltimore, Mary., 1916-1926 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  1916, 1917, 1919, 1920, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Wichita, KS, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Photo Engravers - Washington D.C., 1917-1926 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  1917, 1919, 1920, 1924, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Canada, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Photo Engravers - Minneapolis/St. Paul, MN, 1916-1920 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Photo Engravers - Omaha, NE, 1920-1923 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  1920, 1922, 1923
- Photo Engravers - Newark, NJ, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  1917, 1919, 1920
- Photo Engravers - Albany, NY, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Photo Engravers - Toledo, OH, 1904-1920 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  1904, 1906, 1918, 1920
- Photo Engravers - Youngstown, OH, 1913-1925 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  1913, 1916, 1919, 1925
- Photo Engravers - Oklahoma City, OK, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Photo Engravers - Portland, OR, 1905-1927 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  1905, 1913, 1917-1921, 1925, 1927
- Photo Engravers - Philadelphia, PA, 1917-1924 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  1917, 1919, 1920, 1924
- Photo Engravers - New York, NY, 1919-1927 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  1919-1921, 1924-1927
- Photo Engravers - Rochester, NY, 1905-1924 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  1905, 1918, 1924
- Photo Engravers - Syracuse, NY, 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 105)
- Photo Engravers - Utica, NY, 1918-1920 (Box 5, Folder 106)
- Photo Engravers - Canton, OH, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 107)
- Photo Engravers - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1926 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  1914-1919, 1923-1926
- Photo Engravers - Cleveland, OH, 1912-1926 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  1912, 1914, 1917, 1919, 1924-1926
- Photo Engravers - Buffalo, NY, 1912-1918 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  1912, 1916, 1918
- Photo Engravers - Denver, CO, 1917-1921 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  1917, 1921
- Photo Engravers - St. Louis, MO, 1906-1927 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  1906, 1917, 1923, 1926, 1927
- Photo Engravers - Kansas City, MO, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 113)
- Photo Engravers - Toronto, Canada, 1926-1928 (Box 5, Folder 114)
- Photo Engravers - Duluth, MN, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 115)
- Photo Engravers - Grand Rapids, MI, 1903-1920 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  1903, 1904, 1906, 1919, 1920
- Photo Engravers - Detroit, MI, 1917-1919 (Box 5, Folder 117)
- Photo Engravers - Worcester, MA, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 118)
- Photo Engravers - Springfield, MA, 1918-1927 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  1918, 1920, 1927
- Photo Engravers - Atlanta, GA, 1915-1927 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  1915, 1927
- Photo Engravers - Washington D.C., 1922-1926 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  1922, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Miami, FL, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 122)
- Photo Engravers - Topeka, KS, 1918-1927 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  1918, 1919, 1927
- Photo Engravers - South Bend, IN, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 124)
- Photo Engravers - Des Moines, IA, 1917-1926 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  1917, 1918, 1920, 1926
- Photo Engravers - Indianapolis, IN, 1917-1926 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  1917, 1926
- Pile Drivers - Philadelphia, PA, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 127)
- Pile Drivers - New Orleans, LA, 1915-1919 (Box 5, Folder 128)
- Pile Drivers - New York, NY, 1919-1925 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  1919, 1920, 1922, 1925
- Pile Drivers - Portland, OR, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 130)
- Pile Drivers - Chicago, IL, 1915-1923 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  1915, 1923
- Plate Printers - Washington D.C., 1923 (Box 5, Folder 132)
- Plate Printers and Die Stampers - Boston, MA, 1920-1923 (Box 5, Folder 133)
- Plate Printers and Die Stampers - Albany, NY, 1906-1923 (Box 5, Folder 134)
- Plumbers - New London, CT, 1915-1923 (Box 5, Folder 135)
- Plumbers and Steam Fitters - Atlanta, GA, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 136)
- Plumbers and Steam Fitters - Uniontown, PA, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 137)
- Plumbers - Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1919-1925 (Box 5, Folder 138)
- Plumbers - Williamsport, PA, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 139)
- Plumbers - Providence, RI, 1912-1919 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  1912, 1916, 1919
- Plumbers - Shamokin, PA, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Plumbers - Scranton, PA, 1913-1916 (Box 5, Folder 142)
- Plumbers - Reading, PA, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 143)
- Plumbers - Columbus, OH, 1902-1926 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  1902, 1924, 1926
- Plumbers - Cleveland, OH, 1921-1927 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  1921, 1922, 1927
- Plumbers - Dayton, OH, 1918-1925 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  1918-1921, 1923, 1925
- Plumbers - Carbondale, IL, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Plumbers - Champaign, IL, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Plumbers - Colorado Springs, CO, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Plumbers - Los Angeles, CA, 1917-1923 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  1917, 1919, 1923
- Plumbers - Denver, CO, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Plumbers - Little Rock, AR, 1913-1915 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Plumbers - Macon, GA, 1920-1924 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Plumbers - Birmingham, AL, 1911-1912 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  1911, 1912
- Plumbers - Montgomery, AL, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Plumbers - El Dorado, AR, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Plumbers - San Francisco, CA, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Plumbers - Norwalk, CT, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Plumbers - Cincinnati, OH, 1910-1924 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  1910, 1913, 1916, 1919-1921, 1924
- Plumbers - Niagara Falls, NY, 1903-1924 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Plumbers - Nyack, NY, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Plumbers - Plattsburg, NY, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Plumbers - Poughkeepsie, NY, 1916-1926 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  1916, 1924, 1926
- Plumbers - Miami, FL, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Plumbers - Hendersonville, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Plumbers - Asheville, NC, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Plumbers - Troy, NY, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Plumbers - Utica, NY, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Plumbers - Westchester, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Plumbers - Port Chester, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Plumbers - Fargo, ND, 1903-1905 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Plumbers - Canton, OH, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Plumbers - Chillicothe, OH, 1924-1926 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  1924, 1926
- Plumbers - San Francisco, CA, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Plumbers - Schenectady, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Plumbers - Columbia, SC, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Plumbers - Nashville, TN, 1916-1922 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  1916, 1918, 1920, 1922
- Plumbers - Jackson, TN, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Plumbers - Memphis, TN, 1922-1927 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  1922, 1927
- Plumbers - Hamilton and Windsor, Canada, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Plumbers - Norwich, CT, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Plumbers - Jacksonville, FL, 1919-1926 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  1919, 1920, 1926
- Plumbers - Chicago, IL, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Plumbers - Rochester, NY, 1905-1927 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  1905, 1911, 1914, 1918-1923, 1927
- Plumbers - Suffern, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Plumbers - Suffolk County, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Plumbers - Syracuse, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Plumbers - New Haven, CT, 1914-1921 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  1914, 1919-1921
- Plumbers - Bloomington, IL, 1903-1905 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  1903, 1905
- Plumbers - Bridgeport, CT, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Plumbers - Columbus, OH, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Plumbers - Clearwater, FL, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Plumbers - Daytona, FL, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Plumbers - Belleville, IL, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Plumbers - Washington D.C., 1914-1920 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Plumbers - Stamford, CT, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Plumbers - Westbury, CT, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Plumbers - Wilmington, DE, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Plumbers - Orlando, FL, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Polishers - Barre, VT, 1903-1928 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  1903, 1922, 1928
- Plumbers - Palm Beach, FL, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Plumbers - Bristol, CT, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Plumbers - Danbury, CT, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Plumbers - Hartford, CT, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Potters - National, 1902-1920 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  1902, 1920
- Potters - Wellsville, OH (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Potters - Trenton, NJ, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Potters - Philadelphia, PA, 1900-1919 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  1900-1905, 1911, 1919
- Potters - Pittsburgh, PA, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Potters - East Liverpool, OH, 1920-1926 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Poultry Dressers - San Francisco, CA, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Powder Workers - Columbus, KS, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Printing Pressmen - Pittsburgh, PA, 1913-1919 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  1913, 1916, 1918, 1919
- Printing Pressmen - Seattle, WA, 1909-1918 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  1909, 1910, 1917, 1918
- Printing Pressmen - LaCrosse, WI, 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Printing Pressmen - Philadelphia, PA, 1907-1923 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  1907, 1911, 1921, 1923
- Printing Pressmen - Salt Lake City, UT, 1910-1919 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  1910, 1918, 1919
- Printing Pressmen - St. Louis, MO, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Printing Pressmen - Indianapolis, IN, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Printing Pressmen - Utica, NY, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Printing Pressmen - Charlotte, NC, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Printing Pressmen - Cleveland, OH, 1922-1925 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  1922, 1923, 1925
- Printing Pressmen - Columbus, OH, 1903-1919 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  1903, 1915, 1919
- Printing Pressmen - Washington D.C., 1911-1922 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  1911, 1914, 1917-1922
- Printing Pressmen - Akron, OH, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Printing Pressmen - New York, NY, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Printing Pressmen - Tarrytown-Ossining, NY, 1923-1924 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Printing Pressmen - Tulsa, OK, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Printing Pressmen - Cleveland, OH, 1911-1918 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  1911, 1913, 1916, 1918
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1919-1921 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  1919, 1920, 1921
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Printing Pressmen - Edmonton, Canada, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Printing Pressmen - Ottawa, Canada, 1925-1927 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  1925, 1927
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Printing Pressmen - St. Augustine, FL, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Printing Pressmen - Milwaukee, WI, 1910-1918 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  1910, 1918
- Printing Pressmen - Atlanta, GA, 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  1918, 1919, 1920
- Printing Pressmen - New York, NY, 1909-1925 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  1909-1915, 1918-1925
- Printing Pressmen - Elmira, NY, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 95)
- Printing Pressmen - n/a, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 96)
- Printing Pressmen - Newark, OH, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 97)
- Printing Pressmen - Toledo, OH, 1917-1920 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- Printing Pressmen - Buffalo, NY, 1914-1920 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  1914, 1918-1920
- Printing Pressmen - Youngstown, OH, 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- Printing Pressmen - Knoxville, TN, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 101)
- Printing Pressmen - Cincinnati, OH, 1911-1921 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  1911, 1917, 1919, 1921
- Printing Pressmen - Galveston, TX, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 103)
- Printing Pressmen - Grand Forks, ND, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 104)
- Printing Pressmen - Wichita Falls, TX, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 105)
- Printing Pressmen - Huntington, WV, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 106)
- Printing Pressmen - Spokane, WA, 1917-1925 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  1917, 1918, 1920, 1925
- Press Assistants - Seattle, WA, 1910-1918 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  1910, 1913, 1917, 1918
- Press Assistants - Raleigh, NC, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 109)
- Pressmen and Assistants - Fargo, ND, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 110)
- Press Assistants - Cleveland, OH, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 111)
- Printing Pressmen - Coshocton, OH, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 112)
- Press Assistants - Columbus, OH, 1915-1924 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  1915, 1917, 1919, 1921, 1924
- Printing Pressmen - New York, NY, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 114)
- Printing Pressmen and Assistants - Ft. Worth, TX, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 115)
- Pressmen and Assistants - Sioux Falls, SD, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 116)
- Pressmen and Assistants - Charleston, SC, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 117)
- Pressmen - Cleveland, OH, 1914-1926 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  1914, 1915, 1918-1921, 1926
- Printing Pressmen and Assistants - Portland, OR, 1905-1928 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  1905, 1906, 1909-1920, 1923-1928
- Pressmen and Assistants - Erie, PA, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 120)